http://www.adultfuntoys.co.uk/adultfuntoys/asp/privacy_statement.asp

Privacy Statement
At adultfuntoys.co.uk we believe in plain English.
adultfuntoys will never pass any of your personal details onto any other company. If you opt in to allow us to email you our regular newsletter and occasional special offers then we will. We will never mail you with any other service or products other than those sold by adultfuntoys.
We only collect the minimum personal information required to fulfill your transactions. We collect personal information when you order products from us so that we can send them to you and contact you in the event of a problem.We collect name and email information when you subscribe to our newsletter.We collect Name and address and email address when you request a catalogue.We do not collect any details when you utilise the 'Email Partner' facility.
For audit purposes we will retain copies of credit card transactions
No credit card or personal information will be retained on our computer databases once a transaction has been processed (except email address and name)
If you have any queries please Email us or telephone our office on 0118 979 8286
Executive Sex Toys
Bargains
Realistic Dildoes
Smooth Vibes
Double Dongs
Cock Rings
Nipple Arousers
Lubricants
Wireless Toys
Performance enhancers
Lesbian Toys
Win £100 of Toys
Yes, just put in your details below and you will be entered into our weekly prize draw
Email Address:
Featured Product
£0.00...click for more info...
Best Seller
£0.00...click for more info...
Email Us  |  Company Contact Info  |
FAQ  |
Prices  |
Returns Policy  |
Privacy Statement  |
Cookies Policy  |
Terms & Conditions
Ann Summers Books |
Register Domain Name |
Why a vibrator is better than a man :)
| 6 benefits of sex toys | anal beads | anal dildos | ann summers revolution | benefits of bondage | Benefits of Remote Controlled Sex Toys | benefits of sex toys | bondage tips for beginners | buyers guide to vibrators | campaigning for condoms | cant go wrong with condoms | choosing a lubricant for your dildo | choosing the right lubricant | choosing vibrators | cleaning your sex toys | common health questions about lubricants | condom materials | different types of lubricants | dildos for couples | dildos | dont risk sex without a condom | dos and donts of sex toys | erectile dysfunction | erotic fantasy and sex toys | essential tools for a sensual massage | experts say sex toys good for marriage | finding the g spot | getting creative with lubricants | getting over sex toy phobia | getting the g spot | good vibrations | harness your sexual power | hiding sex toys from your kids | history of sex toys | how sex toys can save your marriage | how to give a sensual massage | how to put on a condom | how to take care of your battery operated vibrator | kinds of cock rings | multiple orgasms for men | multiple orgasms for women | myths about anal beads | myths about vibrators | older couples buying sex toys | penis size how do you measure up | phtalates | plus size lingerie | poor reasons not to buy a sex toy | prostate massage | seduction with lingerie | sex games playing with your partner | sex toys a mums best friend | sex toys and allergy issues | sex toys as a gift | sex toys for lesbian couples | sex toys for women | sex toys spice up your marriage | shake that booty | shopping for sex toys | silicone sex toys | survey says size does matter | taking care of your anal sex toys | taking care of your silicone sex toys | the dildo check list | the growing market for sex toys | the history of sex toys | the myth of vibrator addiction | the rabbit vibrator | the safety of sex toys | too tired for sex | tools of seduction | top five toys for the big boys | touch and tease sensual massages | types of anal beads | unique vibrators | using lubricant with your sex toys | vibrating sex toys for men | which dildos best for you | why sex toys are better than men | why sex toys are better than women |  | adult parties | adult toys | amazing vido | anal sex | a good hand job | bedside companion | bed of roses | best sex toy | better sex | big black butt plug | bingo | bondage tape | booby juice | bunny jumper | cyber chic | devil duckie | double entry vibrator | Ejaculating butt plug | erotic fantasy kit | fireman in the hole | fluffy metal handcuffs | foreplay | foreskin dildo | free sex toys | future tech rabbit | gerries giant | g spot sex toys | hard throb | how to please the
female in bed | hush bunny | jelly tongue | john holmes realistic cock | joni's butterfly | jonis butterfly | lady finger | lilac smoothy | love swing | magic flesh gspot | make a dildo kit | manhood max | marble delight | medium black butt plug | michelles mammoth | mini jelly dong | mr average | mr knobbly | naughty stocking filler | nipple clamps | oral sex | pearl shine bully | perfect 10 ultimate fantasy doll | pink prober | pleasing your partner | premature ejaculation | pretty pink double dong | randy rod | realistic black cock | remote control wireless egg | role playing | rub my duckie black | Seksualne zabawki poland | sex tioys | sex toy for christmas | sex toy kit | sex toys albania | sex toys argentina | sex toys australia | sex toys austria | sex toys belgium | sex toys brazil | sex toys bulgaria | sex toys canada | sex toys china | sex toys croatia | sex toys cuba | sex toys cyprus | sex toys czechrepublic | sex toys denmark | sex toys england | sex toys estonia | sex toys finland | sex toys france | sex toys germany | sex toys greece | sex toys holland | sex toys hungary | sex toys india | sex toys ireland | sex toys italy | sex toys japan | sex toys kenya | sex toys latvia | sex toys lithuania | sex toys luxembourg | sex toys macedonia | sex toys malta | sex toys mexico | sex toys morocco | sex toys new zealand | sex toys nigeria | sex toys pakistan | sex toys poland | sex toys portugal | sex toys romania | sex toys singapore | sex toys slovakia | sex toys slovenia | sex toys south africa | sex toys spain | sex toys sweden | sex toys trinidad and tobago | sex toys turkey | sex toys zambia | sex toys zimbabwe | sexy santa costumes | sexy christmas gift | shiny metal mini vibrator | shirley squirter | silver seducer | slim black butt plug | solid strap on | spanish fly | strawberry sponge vibrator | stud 100 | sx toys | technoflex | the anal balloon | the double bunny | the real mccoy | the ridge | the silencer | the tongue joy | tristar | venus butterfly | vibraters | vibrating extension sheath | vibrating foam rubber duck | vibrating jelly double dong | vibratprs | wet dreamer | wireless remote waterproof vibe |
Site Index
Site copyright © Pilkington Warner Ltd 2002-2020
Web design by Marketsoft
